[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "You're in charge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Was I right to feel scared?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "I think it's totally appropriate to be on guard, because they are incredibly predatory fish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "-- is what it uses to pin down its target prey, which isn't a human being like us --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "But do they attack humans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "-- it's the rays.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "ORGAN: Do hammerheads attack humans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Rarely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What are the most predatory of all the sharks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "Well, there's a number of species that have been known to cross paths with people in a negative way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What is the biggest misconception about sharks, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think the biggest misconception is that they are just a -- a hardwired eating machine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "It would -- really, it would cut me open?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Are they naturally man-eaters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Myth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Do they like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, I think, like any predator, they'll take advantage of easy prey.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "-- on human flesh?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Some shark species actually can sink when they stop swimming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Sharks have no bones?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "They have no bones.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Literally no bones?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "They're made out of cartilage, which is -- which is what they share in common with the skates and the stingrays.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I don't know if that's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) the -- the movie scenes when there's a sort of -- a lot of blood in the water and then you see a -- or a shark descending on them, is that, in reality, how it works?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "ORWIN: You can get a frenzy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do sharks eat each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Sharks actually can display some types of cannibalism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What is this one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "This right here, this is a spiny dog fish, or a spiny shark.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "How dangerous would that shark be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "This is one of the least dangerous species of sharks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "-- and you hear of rock salmon?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What's their favorite eating fish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, I guess it depends the species of sharks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "And let's come back and talk a little bit more about sharks, because everyone is quietly fascinated with them, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Why do we need sharks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Well, it's sort of an interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Does climate change have any impact on the sharks' population?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Climate change certainly can have an impact on the populations of some species of sharks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Is the biggest threat to sharks and their future, as with so many animals, human?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "What do they do to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Well, it -- again, depending on the species of shark.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "And does he -- does he clamp or rip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "He'll hold very tightly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "And you could see it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "You could see it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "By a shark?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "What animal does the shark fear in the water, anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "I think probably there are a number of creatures.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "A shark would be scared of a dolphin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", ":", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "They're incredible -- they have amazing defenses when a -- when dolphins feel threatened by sharks, they will plow at, you know, at torpedo speed into the side of that shark and actually --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "-- kill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", ",", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "-- a bull shark?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "And orcas, killer whales have been known to take on sharks.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Is a great white scared of anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I think a great white may be afraid of other great whites.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do they fight each other?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "They have been known to fight each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "So, this is a stingray tail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "And this is where the sting comes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "That is the weapon of death.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "And how big do they get, a stingray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Huge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "-- to sting them?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "It's a defensive mechanism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "It's a totally defensive mechanism.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Could you die of a stingray sting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ":", "WP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Why are they sometimes called witches purse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, the -- what the -- the reason why they're called witch's purses is actually because of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "And a skate is like a mini stingray without the stick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "It's a little baby, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "This is a little baby that hatched out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Is that the mother there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "This is the mother of these babies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "The skate -- skates aren't dangerous, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "They are not dangerous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "And how long could that take to hatch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "This could -- if the water was warm, it could be in less than a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "How big is it -- how big is this alligator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Well, he's pretty big.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "And how did that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "They were over hunted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "How old is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "And this is probably a couple of years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "How did it get there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "It was an illegal pet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Is that a myth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "It is not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "But even at that size, is it dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "ORWIN: It's not dangerous, but it certainly could hurt you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "You can tell the way the -- the -- the snout is shaped.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Who's more dangerous, crocodiles or alligators?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I would -- to me, they're -- I will swim in alligator country if I feel the risks are low.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Because I think you'd risk a chance of be being, you know, the early buffet of a -- of a crocodile --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "-- are the most dangerous of the reptiles, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I think they're remarkable predators.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "I think it's Fred, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "How many people are keeping these things as pets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "A lot of people, believe it or not, keep them as pets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "How long can they live?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, that's kind of a mystery.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "But they all look a bit docile until they kill you, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "What would he do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Well, if he was in predator mode, basically, what he would be doing is just sort of hunkered down like a submarine low to the water.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Do you see that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Wow!", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "What will this do for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "He will basically hold on very, very tight.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "So they drown you first?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Oftentimes, they will drown you, if they don't crush you first, depending on your size.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Why are you so calm around something that could, at any moment, turn predatory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Well, you know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "What have you got in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "All your nightmares are coming true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "How big is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I'd ask for help, but I know I won't get it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "How big is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "This -- he's 15 feet long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Where do people get these from a pet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "You can buy them in pet shops.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What do they do in the jungle that's so positive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Well, they're a part of that living community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "-- how old is this one?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "This animal is probably five or six years old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 688, "question": "Does she have a name?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 689, "answer": "ORWIN: I think they named it Buddha.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Is it as simple as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "It literally squeezes the life out of you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Do -- could they kill a human?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "It is very possible that a large snake could kill a human.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "Why are you so comfortable around it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Because I know -- I -- I know his behavior.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "What would it do to show that it's stressed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "Well, it would be coil up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 734, "question": "So if I were to ask you, do snakes have legs, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 735, "answer": "I would say they don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Amazon", "Anaconda"]}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "What is the biggest creature this kind of python could eat, who is in -- in the jungle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Well, you know, in the Amazon, the Anaconda, which is a large boa.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ":", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "And this constant thing with its -- its -- what do you call it gut?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "No, this -- that's his chin and this is called buccal pumping.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Zealand"]}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "Of all the creatures that you've found in the ocean or seen, what's been the most amazing moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "I think probably one of the most amazing moments for me was recently filming in New Zealand and actually coming face with a bird species that actually was extinct in the wild and they had rediscovered it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 823, "question": "Could -- couldn't the public around the world be doing a lot more to help conserve the great creatures of the ocean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", ":", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 824, "answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 831, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 832, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNS", "''", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 847, "question": "And the book is called \"Sharks\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 848, "answer": "\"Sharks\" is our new book.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]